Sometimes there really are monsters under your bed.
Dust Bunny is a action, fantasy, thriller film directed by Bryan Fuller.
Ten-year-old Aurora asks her hitman neighbor to kill the monster
under her bed that she claims ate her family.
To protect her, he must battle an onslaught of assassins
while accepting that some monsters are real.
Intriguing Neighbor, played by Mads Mikkelsen.
Aurora, played by Sophie Sloan.
Laverne, played by Sigourney Weaver.
Conspicuously Inconspicuous Man, played by David Dastmalchian.
Brenda, played by Sheila Atim.
Father, played by Caspar Phillipson.
Dust Bunny is a 2025 American fantasy action film written, produced and
directed by Bryan Fuller in his feature film directorial debut.
It stars Mads Mikkelsen, Sophie Sloan, Sheila Atim,
David Dastmalchian, and Sigourney Weaver.
It follows a hit man who is approached by an eight-year-old girl to kill the "monster" under her bed that she
claims "ate" her family, suspecting they were actually killed by dangerous assassins who are after him.
The film premiered at the 2025 Toronto International Film Festival on September 9, 2025,
followed by a theatrical release in the United States on December 12.
The tone is intense.